<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Route Rater Blog</title>
 <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href=""/>
 <updated>2015-03-08T13:56:41+00:00</updated>
 <id></id>
 <author>
   <name>Mike Davies</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Introducing Route Rater</title>
   <link href="/blog/Introducing-Route-Rater.html"/>
   <updated>2015-02-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>/blog/Introducing-Route-Rater</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/introducing-route-rater.png&quot; alt=&quot;routerater&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Route Rater&lt;/em&gt; is an app that enables cyclists to quickly and easily report things about their route, such as bad infrastructure (e.g. lamp-post in a cycle lane), busy or confusing intersections, near-misses with motor vehicles, as well as positive things like cycle-friendly cafes or pubs. Taking inspiration from colour coded European ski-route grades, the app will also provide a map of someone’s area showing them which routes are easier to cycle and which they might want to avoid, and enable the users to contribute their own feedback that helps update the map. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project originated with an idea developed at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://theodi.org/nodes/leeds&quot; title=&quot;ODI Leeds&quot;&gt;ODI Leeds&lt;/a&gt; #hackmyroute day which took place at Munro House, Leeds on 6 Feb 2015. This &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.leedsdatamill.org/hacks-events/hack-my-route-live-blog/&quot; title=&quot;HackMyRoute blog post&quot;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.leedsdatamill.org/&quot; title=&quot;Leeds Data Mill&quot;&gt;Leeds Data Mill&lt;/a&gt; describes what happened on the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the next 6 weeks we’ll be developing a prototype to explore how best to turn the concept into a useful and fun application. As it takes shape we’ll post updates on this blog and create a project wiki for more detailed information on how the prototype is designed and built.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>